{
    "subject": "resource/Players_Association",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Players Association is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8036120533943176,
            "question": "Is the Players Association based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49526894092559814,
            "question": "Where can you find the Players Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49002495408058167,
            "question": "Where is the Players Association headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4224739074707031,
            "question": "To what country does the Players Association belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4221847355365753,
            "question": "What country is associated with the Players Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4129524827003479,
            "question": "From which nation does the Players Association originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4117807447910309,
            "question": "In which nation does the Players Association operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35207611322402954,
            "question": "What is the Players Association's national origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30786556005477905,
            "question": "Which country considers the Players Association as its own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25361689925193787,
            "question": "What is the Players Association's home country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Players Association is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9222_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country considers the Players Association as its own?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9222_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the Players Association's national origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9222_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation does the Players Association operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9222_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9222_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"The US National Soccer Team Players Association is the labor organization for the current members of the United States Men\u2019s National Team, and a membership organization for alumni members of the National Team.\" This information supports the statement that the hometown of The Players Association is indeed United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the U.S. National Soccer Team Players Association, indicating that it serves the interests of members from the United States Men\u2019s National Team and has a mission to grow soccer in America. This aligns with the query stating that the hometown of the Players Association is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}